<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog</title>
    <link>https://sambhavjain.netlify.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 23:14:11 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sambhavjain.netlify.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Failing to compute XOR-functions with an SLP</title>
      <link>https://sambhavjain.netlify.com/blog/post/failing-to-execute-xor-function-with-slps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 23:14:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sambhavjain.netlify.com/blog/post/failing-to-execute-xor-function-with-slps/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: More content would be added later with appropraite images for enhanced understanding of the topic.
Background For some time now, I was wondering to get started with researching deep learning as a domain on my own. So, I waited till my semester exams passed and summer vacations came around. Since, I didn&amp;rsquo;t sent any patch to this year&amp;rsquo;s GSoC Orgs I was unable to become a part of the GSoC Clan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://sambhavjain.netlify.com/blog/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sambhavjain.netlify.com/blog/contact/</guid>
      <description>Here you can find the help you&amp;rsquo;re looking for Are you curious enough to know more about me, mate? Or, have you found some sort of issue/bug with any of the softwares I&amp;rsquo;ve written or would you just like to have quick chat?
Please feel free to contact me using the form below 24&amp;frasl;7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://sambhavjain.netlify.com/blog/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sambhavjain.netlify.com/blog/faq/</guid>
      <description>Meh, more boring stuff. I guess.
whoami I am a student software developer and an aspiring writer from New Delhi, India. I am currently pursuing my B.S. in Computer Science from the University of Delhi. My recent intrests have aligned towards researching about machine learning and deep learning algorithms and getting into the field of AI. In past, I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on (SMP-scale) blockchain-based and web development projects. I like Vanilla-libraries on multiple DBs concurrently, you know.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>